<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Weekly Automation</title>
    <link>http://example.org/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Weekly Automation</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 26 May 2023 20:53:06 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://example.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>A Deep Dive Into Virtualization, Virtual Machines and Docker Containers</title>
      <link>http://example.org/blogs/a-deep-dive-into-virtualization-virtual-machines-and-docker-containers/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2023 20:53:06 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/blogs/a-deep-dive-into-virtualization-virtual-machines-and-docker-containers/</guid>
      <description>Hi guys! 👋
I&amp;rsquo;ve been away for so long but I&amp;rsquo;m back here. 🎉
I thought it would be nice to walk you through a project I worked on while I was away. 🏃‍♀️
The project is simply a containerized web application that allows users to find food trucks near their current location or search for food trucks. 🍔🚚 The app was containerized using Docker to simplify the deployment and scaling.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Error 404</title>
      <link>http://example.org/blogs/error-404/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Apr 2023 17:14:44 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/blogs/error-404/</guid>
      <description>Hey there!
Let&amp;rsquo;s take a look at what happens when you enter a URL into your browser’s address bar.
When you tell your browser you want to visit www.aliexpress.com, your browser is clueless. It doesn&amp;rsquo;t know where that is, which is why it has to translate that address (www.aliexpress.com) to a format it can read. This process is called DNS resolution(Don’t worry if you don&amp;rsquo;t know what that is).
Your browser contacts a DNS server and a conversation like this happens.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The World of Shells and Terminals</title>
      <link>http://example.org/blogs/the-world-of-shells-and-terminals/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Mar 2023 20:33:44 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/blogs/the-world-of-shells-and-terminals/</guid>
      <description>Hey there!
Do you know you don&amp;rsquo;t speak the same language as your computer? While you may be multilingual, your computer only speaks and understands one language. Binary.
Right. You may be able to speak Spanish and English but your computer can only speak ones and zeros.
How do I then make my computer do what I want it to do?
The Kernel: The kernel is the core of the operating system (Think of the engine in a car).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bourne Again Scripting?</title>
      <link>http://example.org/blogs/bourne-again-scripting/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Mar 2023 20:26:59 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/blogs/bourne-again-scripting/</guid>
      <description>While we may all appreciate the role Robert Downey Jr(Tony Stark/Iron man) played in the MCU. I’m pretty sure we all know that a larger part of his conversations and actions in the cinematic universe is based on a script the writers sent to him.
Yeah, I know RDJ was born for the Iron suit, he’s everyone’s favourite(I might have shed a tear when Iron man died) and it is said that most of our favourite lines in the MCU was thought up on the spot by RDJ and the directors thought them good enough to keep them in the movies.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
